export const chapter = "Chapter - 5: Nouns: Gender";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: 'What is the Masculine Gender of "niece"?',
          optionA: "Nephew",
          optionB: "Niece",
          optionC: "Nephress",
          correctAnswer: "Nephew",
        },
        {
          question: 'Which gender category does the word "book" fall into?',
          optionA: "Masculine Gender",
          optionB: "Feminine Gender",
          optionC: "Neuter Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Neuter Gender",
        },
        {
          question: 'What is the Feminine Gender of "hunter"?',
          optionA: "Huntress",
          optionB: "Huntressess",
          optionC: "Huntee",
          correctAnswer: "Huntress",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which category of gender includes nouns that can be either male or female?",
          optionA: "Masculine Gender",
          optionB: "Feminine Gender",
          optionC: "Common Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Common Gender",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How can you change a Masculine Noun into Feminine by altering the word itself?",
          optionA: "By adding ess",
          optionB: "By dropping the last vowel and adding ess",
          optionC: "By using an entirely different word",
          correctAnswer: "By using an entirely different word",
        },
        {
          question: 'Give the Neuter Gender of "pen".',
          optionA: "Pen",
          optionB: "Pencil",
          optionC: "Neuter",
          correctAnswer: "Pen",
        },
        {
          question: 'What is the Common Gender of "friend"?',
          optionA: "Friendess",
          optionB: "Friend",
          optionC: "Friendly",
          correctAnswer: "Friend",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which rule is used to change Masculine Nouns into Feminine by adding ess?",
          optionA: "Rule 1",
          optionB: "Rule 2",
          optionC: "Rule 3",
          correctAnswer: "Rule 1",
        },
        {
          question: 'Provide the Feminine Gender of "author".',
          optionA: "Authoress",
          optionB: "Authress",
          optionC: "Authorette",
          correctAnswer: "Authoress",
        },
        {
          question: "In which gender category do lifeless Nouns belong?",
          optionA: "Masculine Gender",
          optionB: "Feminine Gender",
          optionC: "Neuter Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Neuter Gender",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Masculine Gender is assigned to living Nouns that are __________.",
          optionA: "Female",
          optionB: "Male",
          optionC: "Neuter",
          correctAnswer: "Male",
        },
        {
          question:
            "___________ Gender includes Nouns that can be either male or female.",
          optionA: "Masculine",
          optionB: "Feminine",
          optionC: "Common",
          correctAnswer: "Common",
        },
        {
          question: "Neuter Gender is assigned to ___________ Nouns.",
          optionA: "Living",
          optionB: "Male",
          optionC: "Lifeless",
          correctAnswer: "Lifeless",
        },
        {
          question: "A living Noun is in Feminine Gender if it is ___________.",
          optionA: "Male",
          optionB: "Female",
          optionC: "Common",
          correctAnswer: "Female",
        },
        {
          question:
            "To change a Masculine Noun into Feminine, one of the rules is by adding __________.",
          optionA: "ess",
          optionB: "ish",
          optionC: "en",
          correctAnswer: "ess",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Common Gender includes Nouns that can be either __________ or __________.",
          optionA: "Living, lifeless",
          optionB: "Male, female",
          optionC: "Singular, plural",
          correctAnswer: "Male, female",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Feminine Gender is assigned to a living Noun if it is __________.",
          optionA: "Common",
          optionB: "Female",
          optionC: "Neuter",
          correctAnswer: "Female",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Masculine Nouns can be changed into Feminine by dropping the last vowel and adding __________.",
          optionA: "ish",
          optionB: "ess",
          optionC: "en",
          correctAnswer: "ess",
        },
        {
          question: "The Neuter Gender is assigned to __________ Nouns.",
          optionA: "Male",
          optionB: "Female",
          optionC: "Lifeless",
          correctAnswer: "Lifeless",
        },
        {
          question:
            "By changing the Masculine part into Feminine is one of the rules to change Masculine Nouns into __________.",
          optionA: "Masculine",
          optionB: "Feminine",
          optionC: "Common",
          correctAnswer: "Feminine",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "A living Noun in Feminine Gender is always female.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Common Gender includes Nouns that can only be male.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Neuter Gender is assigned to living Nouns.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adding ess is one of the rules to change Masculine Nouns into Feminine.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Common Gender includes Nouns that can be both male and female.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Feminine Gender is assigned to a living Noun if it is male.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Neuter Gender is assigned to lifeless Nouns.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "One of the rules to change Masculine Nouns into Feminine is by using an entirely different word.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Common Gender includes Nouns that can be neither male nor female.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Neuter Gender is assigned to lifeless and living Nouns alike.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
